Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm
1904-1952
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
LAC0004
87 microfilm reels
The digital edition of the records of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America consist of the correspondence files of the I.B.T. executive office covering the years 1904-1952, with the major portion of the material originating in the 1940's.
Scope and Contents
The digital edition of the records of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America consist of the correspondence files of the I.B.T. executive office covering the years 1904-1952, with the major portion of the material originating in the 1940's. Correspondence is with general executive board members, general organizers, local unions, joint councils, conferences, and trade divisions; the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations; other international unions; government agencies; and the general public. Included with the correspondence are reports, minutes, clippings, transcripts of government hearings and decisions, legal briefs, and copies of local union by-laws. The material details the union's initial struggles for existence and unity, its jurisdictional disputes, its growth in membership and influence, changes in organizing and bargaining techniques and in the trucking and transportation industries, and the increasing strength and political involvement of the labor movement in general.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers presented the paper records to the Wisconsin Historical Society on December 5, 1967.
The International Brotherhood of Teamsters loaned the microfilm edition to the The George Washington University, Gelman Library in 2011 for the digitizing project.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Existence and Location of Originals
The original paper records are housed at the Wisconsin Historical Society. http://www.wisconsinhistory.org/libraryarchives/readroom/labor.asp
Arrangement
Organized into five series: Staff correspondence, Affiliated bodies correspondence and reports, American Federation of Labor correspondence, Other labor organizations correspondence, and General correspondence.
Biographical / Historical
The International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America dates its existence from October 1, 1903. On that date, a convention met to ratify the amalgamation of the Team Drivers International Union, the Teamsters' National Union of America, and other rival groups. They assumed the name International Brotherhood of Teamsters, elected Cornelius P, Shea the first president, and established headquarters in Indianapolis, Indiana. Although amalgamation officially ended the factionalism that had weakened the earlier organizations, in reality conflicts continued. In 1906, the convention split and 35 delegates joined to form a rival organization. Conditions deteriorated and in 1907, Daniel J. Tobin was elected over Shea by a majority of only twelve votes from almost 200 delegates.
The Teamsters did not fade out, in spite of jurisdictional problems. Their membership gradually increased and by 1940 had reached 500,000, making the I.B.T. the largest union in the AFL, By 1952, the Teamsters claimed 1,250,000 members. This large membership also made them one of the richest unions. Their locals numbered over 900 and were located from Alaska to the Canal Zone and from Maine to Hawaii. They were independent in their activities with the International requiring the approval of contracts and by-laws and of strikes if strike benefits were to be paid and adherence to the International constitution.
During these years of growth, the I.B.T.'s structure experienced several changes. Local unions remained the basic unit of organization but other bodies began to be chartered too. Whenever three or more locals existed in close proximity, they were encouraged to band together in a joint council. This council served as an arbiter of disputes and promoted cooperation in bargaining and other activities. Local unions also cooperated in state conferences and in area conferences (Central, Western, New England, etc.). In addition, trade divisions encompassing all locals engaged in a certain type of activity were organized on both a regional and national basis; the I.B.T, was a pioneer of this kind of organization.
With all these structural changes, the governing offices of the union remained generally the same, Daniel J, Tobin served as General President for 45 years, 1907-1952. As I.B.T. General President, Daniel Tobin was a figure of great influence in the American labor movement. He served as AFL Treasurer, 1917-1928, and as an AFL Vicepresident, 1933-1955. He was active in Democratic Party national politics, served as delegate to several Presidential conferences and missions, and was an unofficial candidate for appointment both as Secretary of Labor and as Senator from Indiana. Within the I.B.T., he was a conscientious and well-liked leader with a salty personality. He was adamant in stating from the beginning of his tenure in office that the Teamsters would honor every contract they signed. He was also an out-spoken anti-Communist and led the I.B.T. convention of 1935 in adopting one of the first labor resolutions outlawing Communists from membership. In 1952, Daniel Tobin announced that he would retire from the General Presidency after the convention of that year. When delegates met in Los Angeles, they unanimously elected Dave Beck to the office and Tobin assumed the title President Emeritus.
Labor unions; Labor; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Correspondence; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; Tobin, Daniel Joseph; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); American Federation of Labor
- Staff correspondence, 1904-1952; Series 1; 17 microfilm reels
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent or subject and chronological thereunder.
  Scope and Contents
  The staff correspondence is one of the more complete series in the collection and is especially valuable for the early years. It covers the entire range of activities of the International in its relationships with member locals, joint councils, conferences, trade divisions, the American Federation of Labor and the Congress of Industrial Organizations, other international unions, government agencies, and the general public. The correspondents are (1) Daniel J. Tobin, General President; (2) Thomas Hughes and John Gillespie, General Secretary-Treasurers; and (3) Thomas Flynn, Albert Evans, and others as agents for the General President; corresponding with (l) members of the general executive board; (2) general organizers; (3) auditors; and (U) others of the International staff.
  Particularly notable are the files of the general organizers which frequently contain detailed reports on their activities and the problems encountered, though the files' quantity and quality varies considerably from organizer to organizer. Letters and reports to Tobin while he was away from the office, usually written by Thomas Hughes, Thomas Flynn, or John Gillespie and filed under their names, are another rich source of information, as are similar letters to Tobin from his secretaries, filed under the name Mary O'Neil. Also included in this series is a small amount of material concerning Tobin's personal life, his tenure as administrative assistant to the President, and his possible appointment to the U.S. Senate, as well as some of his speeches and a few clippings about him.
  - Annand, John M., 1947-1950; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 1)
  - Ashton, William H., 1910; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 2)
  - Ashton, William H., 1911; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 3)
  - Ashton, William H., 1912; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 4)
  - Ashton, William H., 1913; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 5)
  - Ashton, William H., 1914; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 6)
  - Ashton, William H., 1915; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 7)
  - Ashton, William H., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 8)
  - Ashton, William H., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 9)
  - Ashton, William H., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 10)
  - Ashton, William H., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 20)
  - Ashton, William H., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 21)
  - Ashton, William H., 1921; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 22)
  - Ashton, William H., 1922; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 23)
  - Ashton, William H., 1923-1924; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 24)
  - Ashton, William H., 1925-1928; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 25)
  - Audits, 1949-1952; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 26)
  - Beck, Dave, 1941-1949; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 26)
  - Beck, Dave, 1950-1952; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 27)
  - Beierle, C. M., 1929; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 28)
  - Bennett, R. J., 1942-1952; Series 1 (Reel 1, Segment 29)
  - Berrell, P. J., 1925-1932; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 1)
  - Blinco, Paul W., 1949-1950; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 2)
  - Borden, Robert A., 1942-1945; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 3)
  - Braddock, J. R., 1947; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 4)
  - Brennan, Sidney L, 1944-1949; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 5)
  - Briggs, George W., 1907-1909; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 6)
  - Briggs, George W., 1910; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 7)
  - Briggs, George W., 1911; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 8)
  - Briggs, George W., 1912; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 9)
  - Briggs, George W., 1913; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 10)
  - Briggs, George W., 1914; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 11)
  - Briggs, George W., 1915; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 12)
  - Briggs, George W., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 2, Segment 13)
  - Briggs, George W., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 1)
  - Briggs, George W., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 2)
  - (skipped), Series 1 (Othertype 3, Folder 3)
  - (skipped), Series 1 (Othertype 3, Folder 4)
  - Briggs, George W., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 5)
  - Briggs, George W., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 6)
  - Briggs, George W., 1921; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 7)
  - Briggs, George W., 1922; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 8)
  - Briggs, George W., 1923; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 9)
  - Briggs, George W., 1924-1925; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 10)
  - Briggs, George W., 1926; Series 1 (Reel 3, Segment 11)
  - Briggs, George W., 1927; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 1)
  - Briggs, Mrs. George W., 1927 Aug.; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 2)
  - Brown, Frank D., 1936; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 3)
  - Brown, Frank D., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 4)
  - Brown, Frank D., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 5)
  - Brown, Frank D., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 6)
  - Brown, Frank D., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 7)
  - Burger, Henry G., 1926-1930; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 8)
  - Burger, Henry G., 1931-1934; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 9)
  - Burger, Henry G., 1935-1937; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 10)
  - Burger, Henry G., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 11)
  - Burke, Peter, 1908-1910; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 12)
  - Burke, Peter, 1911; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 13)
  - Burke, Peter, 1912; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 14)
  - Burrell, Patrick, 1921-1925; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 15)
  - Carter, Leo B., 1943-1947; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 16)
  - Casey, Henry F., 1945-1946; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 17)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1929; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 18)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1936; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 19)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 20)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 21)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1939-1940; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 22)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1941; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 23)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1942-1945; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 24)
  - Casey, Joseph M., 1946-1947; Series 1 (Reel 4, Segment 25)
  - Casey, Michael, 1905, 1907, 1912-1913; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 2)
  - Casey, Michael, 1914; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 1)
  - Casey, Michael, 1915; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 3)
  - Casey, Michael, 1916; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 4)
  - Casey, Michael, 1917; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 5)
  - Casey, Michael, 1918; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 6)
  - Casey, Michael, 1919; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 7)
  - Casey, Michael, 1920; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 8)
  - Casey, Michael, 1921; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 9)
  - Casey, Michael, 1922; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 10)
  - Casey, Michael, 1923; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 11)
  - Casey, Michael, 1924; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 12)
  - Casey, Michael, 1925; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 13)
  - Casey, Michael, 1926; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 14)
  - Casey, Michael, 1927; Series 1 (Reel 5, Segment 15)
  - Casey, Michael, 1928; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 1)
  - Casey, Michael, 1929; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 2)
  - Casey, Michael, 1930; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 3)
  - Casey, Michael, 1931; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 4)
  - Casey, Michael, 1932; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 5)
  - Casey, Michael, 1933; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 6)
  - Casey, Michael, 1934; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 7)
  - Casey, Michael, 1935; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 8)
  - Casey, Michael, 1936; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 9)
  - Casey, Michael, 1937; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 10)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1912-1913; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 11)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1914; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 12)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1915; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 13)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 14)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 15)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 6, Segment 16)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 1)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 2)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1921; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 3)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1922; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 4)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1923; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 5)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1924; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 6)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1925; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 7)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1926; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 8)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1927; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 9)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1928; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 10)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1929; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 11)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1930; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 12)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1931; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 13)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1932; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 14)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1933; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 15)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1934; Series 1 (Reel 7, Segment 16)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1935; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 1)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1936-1937; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 2)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1938-1939; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 3)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 4)
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1941-1944; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 5)
    General
    Note in original finding aid reads "(1945 no corres.)"
  - Cashal, Michael J., 1946-1951; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 6)
  - Charter Application Forms, etc., 1948, undated; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 7)
  - Clay, John G., 1926-1928; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 8)
  - Company Unions, 1945; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 9)
  - Conboy, William J., 1927-1937; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 10)
  - Conboy, William J., 1938-1943; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 11)
  - Conboy, William J., 1944-1952; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 12)
  - Conlin, John J., 1933-1936; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 13)
  - Conlin, John J., 1937-1939; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 14)
  - Conlin, John J., 1940-1941; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 15)
  - Conlin, John J., 1942-1952; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 16)
  - Crumbock, Edward, 1940-1941, 1949, 1951; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 17)
  - Dail, Harry W, 1936-1941; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 18)
  - Davey, Joan, 1945, 1949-1950; Series 1 (Reel 8, Segment 19)
  - Devring, John L., 1914-1915; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 1)
  - Devring, John L., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 2)
  - Devring, John L., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 3)
  - Devring, John L., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 4)
  - Devring, John L., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 5)
  - Devring, John L., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 6)
  - Devring, John L., 1921; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 7)
  - (skipped), Series 1 (Othertype 9, Folder 8)
  - (skipped), Series 1 (Othertype 9, Folder 9)
  - Devring, John L., 1922; Series 1 (Reel 9, Segment 10)
  - Devring, John L., 1923; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 1)
  - Devring, John L., 1924; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 2)
  - Devring, John L., 1925; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 3)
  - Devring, John L., 1926; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 4)
  - Devring, John L., 1927-1929; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 5)
  - Dietrich, Albert, 1944-1952; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 6)
  - Dixon, M. Ralph, 1951-1952; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 7)
  - Dobbs, Farrell, 1939; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 8)
  - Doll, Milton, 1936-1940; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 9)
  - Donovan, Jerry, 1936; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 10)
  - Eddy, Harvey, 1907-1908; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 11)
  - English, John F., 1927, 1929, 1936-1937, 1942-1943, 1948; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 12)
  - Evans, Albert, 1949-1951; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 13)
  - Farrell, Thomas J., 1907-1908, 1918, 1921, 1925; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 14)
  - Farrell, Thomas J., 1939-1940, 1944, 1947; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 15)
  - Flynn, Thomas E., 1941-1950; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 16)
  - Forkey, Joseph, 1907-1909; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 17)
  - Frederick, Cliff, 1952; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 18)
  - Geary, John, 1909-1915; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 19)
  - Geary, John, 1916-1917; Series 1 (Reel 10, Segment 20)
  - Geary, John, 1918-1923; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 1)
  - Geary, John, 1924-1927; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 2)
  - Geary, John, 1928-1931; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 3)
  - Geary, John, 1932-1933; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 4)
  - Geary, John, 1934; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 5)
  - Geary, John, 1935-1937; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 6)
  - Geary, John, 1938; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 7)
  - Geary, John, 1939-1942; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 8)
  - General Executive Board - Meetings, 1907-1908, 1936; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 9)
  - General Executive Board - Members, 1940, 1945; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 10)
  - Gibbons, Harold, 1949-1950; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 11)
  - Gibbons, W. J., 1907-1908; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 12)
  - Gillespie, John M., 1908, 1920, 1925-1929, 1931-1933; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 13)
  - Gillespie, John M., 1934-1937; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 14)
  - Gillespie, John M., 1938-1940; Series 1 (Reel 11, Segment 15)
  - Gillespie, John M., 1941-1943; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 1)
  - Gillespie, John M. - Letters of Condolence, 1946; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 2)
  - Golden, George F., 1908-1910; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 3)
  - Golden, George F., 1912-1914; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 4)
  - Golden, George F., 1915-1916; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 5)
  - Golden, George F., 1917-1919; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 6)
  - Golden, George F., 1920-1925; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 7)
  - Goudie, Leslie G., 1933-1937; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 8)
  - Goudie, Leslie G., 1938-1939; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 9)
  - Goudie, Leslie G., 1940-1943; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 10)
  - Grace, Lawrence A., 1908-1909; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 11)
  - Grace, Lawrence A., 1910; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 12)
  - Grace, Lawrence A., 1912-1915; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 13)
  - Hancock, William D., 1950-1952; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 14)
  - Hart, William F., 1921-1925; Series 1 (Reel 12, Segment 15)
  - Hart, William F., 1926-1932; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 1)
  - Hickey, Thomas L., 1951-1952; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 2)
  - Hindley, Kenneth M., 1943; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 3)
  - Hoffman, R. J., 1907-1908; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 4)
  - Hoffman, Valentine, 1908-1910; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 5)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1906-1909; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 6)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1910-1912; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 7)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1913-1915; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 8)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1916-1918; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 9)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1919-1925; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 10)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1926-1929; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 11)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1930-1933; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 12)
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1934-1940; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 13)
  - Humphrey, Fred W., 1912-1913; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 14)
  - Insurance, 1947-1952; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 15)
  - Jennings, John J., 1907-1909; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 16)
  - Jennings, P. H. (Harry), 1912-1915; Series 1 (Reel 13, Segment 17)
  - Jennings, P.H. (Harry), 1916-1919; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 1)
  - Jennings, P.H. (Harry), 1920-1925; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 2)
  - Jennings, P.H. (Harry), 1940, 1942-1946; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 3)
  - Kaplan, David, 1944-1951; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 4)
  - Keul, Carl, 1942-1952; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 5)
  - Kidd, George, 1928-1930; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 6)
  - King, George W., 1915-1920; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 7)
  - King, John H., 1948-1952; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 8)
  - Lady Auxiliaries, 1938, 1944-1945, 1951; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 9)
  - Lannan, N. J., 1930-1940; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 10)
  - Lewis, Dexter L., 1941-1946; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 11)
  - Lyons, Thomas J., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 12)
  - Lyons, Thomas J., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 13)
  - Lyons, Thomas J., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 14)
  - Lyons, Thomas J., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 15)
  - MacArthur, A. F., 1947-1949; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 16)
  - MacArthur, L. T., 1910; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 17)
  - McGill, Patrick, 1910; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 18)
  - McGill, Patrick, 1911; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 19)
  - McGill, Patrick, 1912; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 20)
  - Mclntyre, James, 1946; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 21)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 22)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 23)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 24)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 25)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1941; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 26)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1946; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 27)
  - McLaughlin, John P., 1950; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 28)
  - Mandoiza, Clarence, 1952; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 29)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1908; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 30)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1913; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 31)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1916; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 32)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1917; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 33)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1918; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 34)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1922; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 35)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1923; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 36)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1926; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 37)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1927; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 38)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1928; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 39)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1929; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 40)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1930; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 41)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1931; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 42)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1932-1933; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 43)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1934; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 44)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1935; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 45)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1944; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 46)